buddydev.com 2017-02-15

# Privacy Policy • BuddyDev

Effective Nov 15 ,2009

Table Of Contents:

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * The Way We Use Information:
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * Our Suggestions
  * How To Contact Us

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BuddyDev.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address(if applicable)  
Email address  
Company Details(if applicable)

### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our premium content as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your profile.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error if you are unable to update it yourself.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### Our Suggestions

Do not disclose the information, you don’t want to make available publicly.Any information you fill in your profile, will be available publicly except your email.So please use it wisely,or inform us to de-list your profile from the members directory.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please mail us at contact@buddydev.com.
